Hey everyone, it's jumpsuit or catsuit time again. I have two new catsuits from Fashion Nova
that are the same, just different colors and really cool material. And I'm also already
wearing a bodysuit from Fashion Nova and I wanted to try it on for the first time. I'm not convinced
by the combination with the leggings though. But since this is just a start outfit, I will
think about something else to wear with the bodysuit for the next time. And we're going to
start with the first catsuit. Let's do pink!
Flashback
okay that was a bit of work because it's really tight i'm wearing size extra small
and it is stretchy but for getting into it the first time i had to work out basically
but now it fits really tight and i think it looks really good
even though it's pink but it's really snug what I love about it is that the arms and legs are
really long like almost too long especially with the legs but I'm not complaining about that
because it's not that usual and yeah I think the lines look really great and when I talk about
these lines and a cut here. I think Fashion Nova was heavily inspired by a design from Mugler.
They also had a catsuit with pretty similar design and also the same material. It was sold out really
fast and to be honest it was really expensive. And then Fashion Nova threw these on the market
and yeah well I ordered them. Now about the material it's really difficult to explain. I'll
best show you and say something about it when I wear the black one. Alright the
black one. It's size small so size larger than the pink one. I wanted to try both
sizes and to be honest this one is a bit more comfortable because it's longer and
not as tight but I think the extra small looked a bit better.
but I think it's also okay.
Looking good.
Bit more wrinkles due to
bigger sizing maybe.
Okay, the material. It's a hard
question. I'm not entirely sure
how I would call it.
I've seen it a few times now as I said
with Mugler, with
several other Fashion Nova
items, some leggings.
Kind of a new trend material.
And it's, I'd
say it's kind of PVC
but on the other hand it has more structure to it and you can also tell it's a different sound
it's stretchier than PVC by far I don't know really what it's called
I mean we can agree that it's some kind of coated fabric PU coating any
anyhow I don't know really to be honest if you know it leave a comment down below you know I
think it sounds a bit like you know when you were a kid like the rulers that had different pictures
on them when you turned them around like flip-flop pictures I think that's the kind of a sound and
material that reminds me of it's very specific I know it also has a different shine to it kind of
absorbs the light more but it's also reflective. I don't know it's really weird. Anyway I think
this is a great basic catsuit and since it's not too thick it's also not too warm so not too sweaty
good for warmer weather and I'm definitely going to keep this and wear it again and use it as a
base for throwing accessories or harnesses onto it and yeah what else can I say I don't know I
I think that's it for today. I hope you leave a comment and a thumbs up for this video.
Subscribe to my YouTube channel or even check out my Patreon for more behind the scenes content.
And I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!